litecam.net 2011-05-31

# Innoheim Privacy Policy

This document states the innoheim privacy policy regarding information you may provide with while you visit innoheim's web site, www.innoheim.com.

**Collecting Personal Information**

innoheim provides our customers with a variety of services. Customers can engage in most of the activities without providing their personal information when they visit innoheim's web site. For the customers requiring some of the specific contents from this site, they may be asked to provide personal information such as their names, e-mail addresses, mailing addresses, phone numbers and so on in order for Infostrider to better serve these customers.

**Internet Connectivity**  
Once You have purchased a license from INNOHEIM in order to continue to use the Software, You may be required to activate the Software through the Internet. There are technological measures within the Software that are designed to prevent unlicensed use of the Software. INNOHEIM will use those measures to confirm You have a valid licensed copy of the Software. When the Software automatically connects to the Internet, an Internet protocol address (“IP Address”) that is associated with your current Internet connection is sent to innoheim authorization server along with System information including CPU, BIOS, Motherboard name, OS, graphics card, and user information including license code, user name and e-mail address which were entered in the first page of the installation screen to initiate the program authentication process. 

**Using the Information Collected**

When you provide innoheim with your personal information, you must be aware that your information could be used for some purposes such as statistical analysis, etc. by restricted Infostrider personnel and its business partners without notifying you. In addition, innoheim can share your information in response to legal requests.

**Using Cookies**

When you visit innoheim's web site, we use cookies to track your visit. Not only does the use of cookies record your preferences so that you could use our web site more easily, but also cookies are used to improve our web site.

**Privacy Statement Changes**

innoheim's privacy statement will be updated according to material changes regarding this statement. In case of updating this privacy statement, notice will be recognized on the web site. 

If you have questions, please contact [innoheim](mailto:support@innoheim.com)
